[{"answer": "What'd he die of", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "The official cause", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "For starters I'd like to know why she left the house and didn't report the death", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Did I say it was a natural death", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You're on vacation, remember?  You're supposed to be relaxing", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " This is not relaxing", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " This is not relaxing", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Really", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "my friend, I'm the only criminal attorney you have", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "It didn't get there from me", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "That's not an answer", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Tastes can change", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Hi, my friend", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I hardly know him.  He wanted me and he couldn't have me", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " It won't be that hard", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You and me", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "No", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " That's not good enough, Goddamit", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No, I don't have to believe you.  The jury has to believe you and answers like he's lying or she's mistaken aren't going to convince them", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "-- But it's Sunday", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " I gotta go.  I'll call you later", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Tell the court about that, please", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Did you see Mr. my friend the day before his death", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I'm glad you have such confidence in me", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " What does that mean?  You've been thinking about the case?  Or you thought everything out before you killed my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I'm talking to you as a friend now. Don't ruin your life, your career for her.  She'll spit you out when this is over", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Really?  What does an attorney speak to his client about at her house until three o'clock in the morning", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I've been waiting for you to get back", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "No", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Mr. my friend, what was your relationship with Miss my friend", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "How long were you together", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Fine.  The doctors say if I keep taking care of myself I can live to be a very old man", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "It didn't", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Why did she say she was leaving", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Why do you think she left you", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "She was", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I knew you were thinking that.  I could see it in your eyes today in the courtroom.  You're wrong, my friend. I need you to believe that", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I do need you.  No matter what you think of me", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "You can think whatever you want, my friend", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "No", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "-- And what did Dr. my friend do after you stopped seeing him", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Did he make your life miserable", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Your Honor", "docId": "Body-of-Evidence.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I can back it up", "qsentId": 48}]